

PROFILE

Self-taught web developer and experienced HR consultant. Thirsty for challenges of any kind. I deeply enjoy working on projects with team-mates. I am extremely enthusiastic and self-motivated. Above all, I'm a very hard working professional.

Brigittenau, Vienna, Austria

mfconsolani@outlook.com

26 years old

(\$\) Argentine/Spanish



Click to check it out!



github.com/mfconsolani



/mauro-consolani



+43 6602 068914

EXPERIENCE

WEB DEVELOPER

4HAPPYDEVS (2020 - PRESENT)

- Frontend web apps development based on HTML5, CSS3 & Bootstrap4
- Backend web apps development based on Python (Flask)
- Deployment on Heroku

 4 Happy Devs Web Site

HR MANAGEMENT CONSULT.

PROVINCIAL MINISTRY OF EDUCATION (2019 - 2020)

- Management reporting and projects follow-up
- Personnel administration
- Customer service

• HR recruitment

HR COORDINATOR*

PROVINCIAL BUREAU OF ADMINISTRATIVE MODERNIZATION (2017-2019)

(2018-2019)

- Development and implementation of a performance assessment system
- In charge of 5 team partners

HR ANALYST

(2017-2018)

- Formalization of internal processes
- Development of internal training program
- Tasks management, internal communication and assessment of work environment

EDUCATION

SELF-TAUGHT DEVELOPER

UDEMY, EDX, BOOKS AND WHEREVER KNOWLEDGE LIVES! (2019 - PRESENT)

Check my website!

BA IN HUMAN RESOURCES

CATHOLIC UNIVERSITY OF LA PLATA - ARGENTINA (2014 - 2018)

SKILLS

TECHNICAL

- Python
- HTML5 & CSS3
- Bootstrap 4
- JavaScript (in progress)
- HR Management
- HR Recruiting
- English (Advanced)
- Spanish (Mother tongue)

JIRA

• Git & Github

SOFT

- Self-motivated
- Problem-solving
- Methodical
- Teamwork

- Life-long learner
- Management
- Communication
- Integrity

INTERESTS & MORE...

WEB APPLICATION

PASTO A PASTO - WEB APP (2020 - PRESENT)

Pasto a Pasto web app is meant to measure the forage offer level for stockbreeding establishments to optimize their productivity. Driven by Scrum methodology, we were able to deploy the MVP after three weeks. Git & GitHub flow, JIRA, team organization, team communication and logical creativity were the foundation stones for this project. Check it out! www.pastoapasto.com.ar

CRAFT BEER ENTREPREUNERSHIP

ARCCADIA (2017 - 2019)

Arccadia was built by four very close friends and myself. We started brewing 20lts. per month and reached a maximum of 400lts. per month. We learned about administration, production, organization and business but best of all, we developed a high teamwork spirit.